Guide to the New-York Historical Society Collection of New York City Miscellaneous Manuscripts, circa 1614-1933 (bulk 1641-1900) MS 443.19
New-York Historical Society
- Last piece of ticker tape from October 29, 1929, 1929 October 29 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  Total Sales Today 16.388.700 …. Good Night. Oct. 29.1929 (Stock Market Crash)
- Papers relating to the Exposition of Old New York in the Fifth Avenue Building Company (4 folders), 1933 (Box 9, Folder 22-25)
  Exhibition ran from March 25, 1933 to April 15, 1933. It related to the history of Madison Square and the old Fifth Avenue Hotel. 10 photographs of the exhibition. Brief History of the Plot of the Fifth Avenue Building. Pamphlet, "This Week in New York" March 19-March 25, 1933.